(Leonard:)Don't know.
(Penny:)I wonder if it's from, like, ancient Rome...
(Penny:)...where they'd actually chop
somebody's ass off and then go, "Here."
(Penny:)You know, to appease Loseroneous,
the god of losers.
(Sheldon:)I am not a loser.
(Sheldon:)Pictionary is not a true test
of any real intelligence or skill.
(Leonard:)In all fairness,
Pictionary has verbal skills, visual skills.
(Leonard:)A pretty well-rounded game.
(Sheldon:)Lot of big talk from a man
who can't draw a chocolate chip cookie.
(Penny:)Fine, pick another game.
Amy and I will beat you at anything.
(Sheldon:)All right. Let's play...
(Sheldon:)...Physics Fiesta.
- Oh, come on. What is that?
- It's a game that I just invented...
(Sheldon:)...in which the participants answer
physics questions in remedial Spanish.
(Howie Mandel:)Uh...
Donde esta el boson de Higgs?